<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BehaviorQuiz</string>
    <string name="quizresult_buttontext">Ok</string>
    <string name="preference_file_key">jack.behaviourquiz.PREFERENCE_FILE_KEY</string>
    <string name="menu_settings_text">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_home_text">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_about_text">About</string>
    <string name="quiz_explanation_title">Try again! Explanation:</string>
    <string name="about_dialog_title">About</string>
    <string name="about_dialog_message">Welcome to the ABA Wizard app! This app is centered on the BACB Fourth Edition Task List to make sure you understand the important concepts to pass the exam. We don’t go in to anything that wouldn’t be on the exam. With over 1400 practice questions, immediate feedback with explanations, and references you’ll feel confident in your exam preparedness. \n\nThe app is simple to use. Each red button on the home page is a section of the BACB Fourth Edition Task list. Once a section is selected, an array of quizzes will be displayed. There is one quiz for each task list item, and each quiz contains 10 practice questions. You must answer all 10 questions correctly to pass off that quiz. Pass off all of the quizzes to be completely prepared for the exam.\n\nTest your knowledge by taking a random quiz! 10 questions are pulled at random and could be from any task list item. \n\nIf you have any concerns regarding the content of the questions, or recommendations for the app, please contact us at our website ABA-Wizard.com. We will answer any of your questions, and would love your feedback. Feel free to check out the references below which were used in the creation of the practice questions. \n\n\nReferences:\n\nBinder, C. and Watkins, C. L. (2013), Precision Teaching and Direct Instruction: Measurably Superior Instructional Technology in Schools. Perf. Improvement Qrtly, 26: 73–115. doi: 10.1002/piq.21145\n\nCipani, E., &amp; Schock, K. M. (2011). Functional behavioral assessment, diagnosis, and treatment: A complete system for education and mental health settings. New York, NY: Springer.\n\nCooper, John O., Heron, Timothy E.Heward, William L.. (2007) Applied behavior analysis /Upper Saddle River, N.J. : Pearson/Merrill-Prentice Hall,\n\nDattilo, J. and Camarata, S. (1991), FACILITATING CONVERSATION THROUGH SELF-INITIATED AUGMENTATIVE COMMUNICATION TREATMENT. Journal of Applied Behavior Analysis, 24: 369–378. doi:10.1901/jaba.1991.24-369\n\nHart, B. and Risley, T. R. (1975), INCIDENTAL TEACHING OF LANGUAGE IN THE PRESCHOOL1. Journal of Applied Behavior Analysis, 8: 411–420. \n\nKlatt, K. P., &amp; Morris, E. K. (2001). The premack principle, response deprivation, and establishing operations. The Behavior Analyst, 24(2), 173–180.\n\nLafasakis, M. and Sturmey, P. (2007), TRAINING PARENT IMPLEMENTATION OF DISCRETE-TRIAL TEACHING: EFFECTS ON GENERALIZATION OF PARENT TEACHING AND CHILD CORRECT RESPONDING. Jnl of Applied Behav Analysis, 40: 685–689. doi: 10.1901/jaba.2007.685-689\n\nMartin, T. L., Yu, C. T., Martin, G. L., &amp; Fazzio, D. (2006). On Choice, Preference, and Preference for Choice. The Behavior Analyst Today, 7(2), 234–241.\n\nReid, Dennis H. "Supervisor's guidebook : evidence-based strategies for promoting work quality and enjoyment among human service staff." Morganton, N.C. : Habilitative Managment Consultants, 2012.\n\nSherman, J. G. (1992), REFLECTIONS ON PSI: GOOD NEWS AND BAD. Journal of Applied Behavior Analysis, 25: 59–64. doi:10.1901/jaba.1992.25-59\n\nSkinner, B. F. (1957). Verbal behavior. New York: Appleton-Century-Crofts.\n\nSy, J. R., Borrero, J. C. and Zarcone, J. (2009), PARAMETRIC ANALYSIS OF PRESESSION EXPOSURE TO EDIBLE AND NONEDIBLE STIMULI. Journal of Applied Behavior Analysis, 42: 833–837. doi:10.1901/jaba.2009.42-833\n\nTourinho, E. Z. (2006). Private Stimuli, Covert Responses, and Private Events: Conceptual Remarks. The Behavior Analyst, 29(1), 13–31.\n\nWard-Horner, J., &amp; Sturmey, P. (2010). COMPONENT ANALYSES USING SINGLE-SUBJECT EXPERIMENTAL DESIGNS: A REVIEW. Journal of Applied Behavior Analysis, 43(4), 685-704. Retrieved from https://search.proquest.com/docview/818745176?accountid=166077</string>

</resources>
